Why?
The medicine
doesn't work.
Your body needs time to recover.
Don't worry.
Ah!
You!
There's something wrong with the medicine.
Yes.
I poisoned
the medicine.
But
it was chronic before.
Today
I increased the dosage.
You...
Don't think I don't know
you sent Chen Shusheng
to find your eldest son in the UK.
Hmph.
What a pity.
Too late.
He has
died.
By the way,
I forgot to tell you.
Lin Jiming
is the son of me and Wu Zhanshan.
He
is the true heir of the Lin family.
You...
Son,
I'm sorry.
I'm useless.
Please be okay.
[The truth has torn us open and the wound won't stop bleeding.]
[We've all become ghosts trapped in the past.]
[But once you step]
[on some paths,]
[you can only go deeper into the night,]
[until destruction,]
[or rebirth.]
Jiang Lin,
I can't pretend anymore.
I'm so tired.
I know.
I know everything.
Am I not incredibly foolish?
I've searched for three years,
hated someone for three years,
but in the end,
I hated the wrong person,
and searched for the wrong one.
Don't be like this.
Xiaoyu.
Ji Ming is gone.
My child is gone.
I have nothing left.
Jiang Lin.
You're all I have.
Please help me.
You work in the court.
I want to sue...
I want to sue Wen Shiyi,
Wu Zhanshan.
I want to sue them.
I want them to pay.
They must pay.
Xiaoyu,
calm down.
You need direct evidence to sue.
Just based on these guesses,
you can't even file a case.
If there's no evidence,
I'll go find it.
There must be some.
I'll investigate Wen Shiyi,
the 500,000 pounds,
and Zhou Qi.
There must be evidence.
Gu Qingyu,
look at yourself.
If you use illegal means to take revenge and kill,
what's the difference between you and Wen Shiyi?
Do you think Wang Jiming would want this?
Look at my mom.
She loves you so much.
Do you think she would want this?
The law is a weapon,
but not to be used like this.
The flames of revenge will consume you first.
Wake up.
Tell me what to do.
I've waited for three years.
I've hated for three years.
I'm afraid that
I can't hold on
for another three years.
Yu,
I'm really tired, Jiang Lin.
I can't hold on anymore.
Cry.
Crying will make you feel better.
Trust me.
The law will definitely take the right way
to make those who should pay the price pay.
Trust me.
You two murderers!
Mr. Wen,
I gave you the identity of Lin Jiming,
and everything that comes with it.
Wake up and
be the heir you're supposed to be,
not acting like a lunatic here.
Mr. Wen.
Shut up!
You have no right to speak!
What?
Uncomfortable?
Then you should take away
what's most important to me now.
For example,
the Lin Group.
Do you have the ability to do this?
Yes.
My dear son,
Zhanshan,
Wrap the flowers on the ground
and give them to Guan Law Firm.
Tell her
they are a farewell gift
from our Lin Group.
Are you asleep?
What's going on with Mr. Lin?
I heard...
Shh!
Stop talking!
Mr. Wen said
no one is allowed to spread the news.
Let's go.
Your farewell gift
is on the way.
I'm sorry.
Yes, it's me.
Tomorrow,
you go back to the Lin Group
and support me unconditionally.
I will fulfill
I will fulfill my promise.
[Is the farewell gift]
[a forewarning of death]
[or a trumpet call to battle?]
[Wen Shiyi,]
[I will continue to walk this road]
[of the unlicensed edge.]
[Until one of us]
[plunges into the abyss.]